

MUHAMAD IRKHAM MAULANA

6281228322893 | irkhammuhamad80@gmail.com

Jalan Pisang Kipas, Lowokwaru, Kota Malang

Muhamad Irkham Maulana is a student at Brawijaya University in the Information Technology Education study program. Irkham has skills and expertise regarding problem solving, partnership experience and extensive relationships which have been proven by holding his own activities several times successfully. Irkham has a high enthusiasm for learning new things and a strong fighting determination

Work Experiences

DIGITAL CREATIVE - MALANG

Sep 2023 - Present

Staff Social Media Specialist

MINDCARE_ID - INDONESIA

Mar 2023 - Present

Founder

A platform that focuses on mental health which has regular activities, namely online counseling and material on mental health and has an active discussion group on a national scale

PRODUCTIVZEE - INDONESIA

Jul 2021 - Present

Co Founder

A platform that focuses on development and self-improvement which has more than 2 years of experience and has also successfully carried out several events and achievements

INFO SEPUTAR PENDIDIKAN - Indonesia

Aug 2019 - Present

Founder

A platform that focuses on educational issues in Indonesia as well as a media partner account that has more than 3 years of experience and is trusted by more than 100 collaborations

UMAR UB - MALANG Sep 2022 - May 2023

Staff Muda Humas

An organization under the auspices of MRP which focuses on the world of Islam and da'wah as well as a liaison between students at UB who have the same goal focus, namely spreading da'wah and studies in the campus environment

Education Level

SMAN 2 Nganjuk - Nganjuk

Jul 2020 - Jul 2022

Universitas Brawijaya - Malang

Aug 2022 -

Organisational and Committee Experience

BRAWIJAYA MUDA - Malang

Aug 2023 - Present

Staff Transcop

Activities under the auspices of EM UB which focus on introducing and promoting UB to schools both offline and online, also holding SNBT tryouts and national scale talk shows

 Become a transcorp staff who has the task of being responsible for taking care of all matters relating to facilities and infrastructure during activities

Gebyar Ramadhan MRPUB - Malang

Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

Staff Media Sosial Specialist

Ramadhan celebration activities are under the auspices of MRP and organized by UMAR which has various activities during Ramadan such as routine studies before sunset, sahur together, breaking the fast together, food festivals, awards to the best mosque administrators, on a scale in Malang City

• Become a specialist social media staff who has the task of managing information conveyed to the general public, such as making broadcast reminders of activities, editing posters for da'wah studies, creating stock of study posters about Ramadan

MENTORING CAMABA 2023 - Indonesia

Nov 2022 - Apr 2023

Chief Excecutive

Mentoring and training for prospective new students class of 2023 with various events such as holding FGDs, self-development webinars, providing material regarding Scholarships, College entrance procedures, and sharing with outstanding students

• Be responsible for all events held and provide direction to team divisions working on their respective tasks

Staff Public Relation

The highlight of the event and the closing of the introduction of the FILKOM UB environment to new students of FILKOM UB class of 2022 under the auspices of BEM MINISTRY OF PSDM FILKOM UB

• Become a public relations staff who is responsible as a liaison between related parties, as well as creating various content, capturing moments, managing social media accounts, and being LO

MTQMN - Malang Sep 2023 - Present

Staff LO

Student Musabaqah Tilawatil Qur'an (MTQ) is an event held every two years by the Ministry of Education and Culture in an effort to develop student talent in the field of Musabaqah Tilawatil Qur'an (MTQ). The 2023 activity will be held at Brawijaya University, Malang.

• Become a LO (Liaison Officer) or be a liaison between guests and the committee to communicate with each other and coordinate for the success of an event in the activities carried out during the event

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Achievements (2022): Become the best volunteer in commemoration of national anti-narcotics day by MERCU BUANA UNIVERSITY
- Achievements (2022): 3rd place in the Sharia Economics Competition by HMPS AHMAD DAHLAN UNIVERSITY
- Achievements (2023): Become a Volunteer for the Campaign "Life becomes healthier and become young Indonesians who care about their own health and the environment" from chemical pharma and BUMN activities by the Social Connect platform